- Is it a secret?
- No, it's a nitrogen laser.
(Leonard:)It'll cook your eyeball like a soft-boiled egg.
Oh, might wanna put a sign on it.
There's a sign right there.
Ah, "Danger." Sure, sure.
So, what's that?
(Leonard:)That is an integrated ion trap
and time-of-flight mass spectrometer.
Wow. High techie-techie.
(Penny:)What's this little box?
(Leonard:)That is a pencil sharpener.
Oh, low techie-techie.
So, what are you working on now?
- It's actually pretty neat.
- Yeah?
(Leonard:)It's a front-projected holographic display...
...combined with laser based
finger tracking. Here, I'll show you.
(Leonard:)Put this pencil over here.
(Penny:)Sharp, thanks to the machine
we saw earlier.
(Leonard:)Very good.
(Leonard:)Then a laser will map
the reflective surface...